Macbeth Gallery
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Correspondence Files, 1838-1968, n.d., Series 1:; (Box 1-95, 163-164, OV 165; 96.2 linear feet)
  - Correspondence, 1838-1968, n.d., 1.1:
    - Proctor, Jessie (2622), 1916 (Box 67)
    - Providence Art Club (NMc19/2622), 1898, 1916-1922 (Box 67)
    - Provincetown Art Shop (2622), 1930-1932 (Box 67)
    - Prudential Insurance Company of America, 1932-1954 (Box 67)
    - Pruyn, Caspar L. (2622), 1920-1923 (Box 67)
    - Pruyn, Edward Lansing (2622), 1923-1932 (Box 67)
    - Public Library of Newark New Jersey (2613), 1910-1942 (Box 67)
    - Pulsifer, Harold T. (2622), 1937-1940 (Box 67)
    - Pulsifer, L. V. and Nathan T. Pulsifer (2622), 1913-1937 (Box 67)
    - Pumpelly, Esther P. and Harold A. Pumpelly (2622), 1937 (Box 67)
    - Purdy, W. Frank (2622), 1929-1937 (Box 67)
    - Purnell Galleries (2622), 1913-1932, 1951 (Box 67)
    - Purves, Helen Ogden (Mrs. Alexander; 2622), 1937 (Box 67)
    - Pushman, Hovsep (NMc44/2622), 1916-1930, (3 folders) (Box 67)
    - Putnam, Arthur and Grace Storey Putnam (NMc10/2622), 1908-1923, n.d., (3 folders) (Box 67)
    - Putnam, Louis and William A. Putnam (NMc19/2622-2623), 1911-1917, n.d. (Box 67)
    - Putnam, Mrs. William A., Jr. (2622), 1937 (Box 67)
    - Pyle, Anne P. and Howard Pyle (NMc10/2623), 1905-1914 (Box 67)
    - Pyne, George F. and R. L. Pyne (NMc10), 1897-1905 (Box 67)
    - P, Miscellaneous: Illegible, 1905, 1920, n.d. (Box 67)
    - P, Miscellaneous: Paa-Pag (2616-2617), 1898-1950 (Box 67)
    - P, Miscellaneous: Pai-Pal (2616-2617), 1899-1952, (contains photo-postcard of artist Robert Lucian Paley in his studio ca. 1916) (Box 67)
    - P, Miscellaneous: Pam-Pari (2616-2617), 1895-1952 (Box 67)
    - P, Miscellaneous: Park-Parr (2616-2617), 1899-1956 (Box 67)
    - P, Miscellaneous: Pars-Part (2616-2617), 1896-1950 (Box 67)
    - P, Miscellaneous: Pas-Pat (2616-2617), 1895-1953 (Box 67)
    - P, Miscellaneous: Pau-Pay (2616-2617), 1895-1952 (Box 67)
    - P, Miscellaneous: Pea-Pec (2616-2617), 1895-1952 (Box 67)
    - P, Miscellaneous: Ped-Pen (2616-2617), 1907-1955 (Box 67)
    - P, Miscellaneous: Peo-Per (2616-2617), 1911-1954 (Box 67)
    - P, Miscellaneous: Pes-Pey (2616-2617), 1895-1956 (Box 67)
    - P, Miscellaneous: Pf-Phe (2616-2617), 1896-1959 (Box 67)
    - P, Miscellaneous: Phi (2616-2617), 1896-1952 (Box 67)
    - P, Miscellaneous: Pho-Pie (2616-2617), 1899-1953 (Box 67)
    - P, Miscellaneous: Pif-Pit (2616-2617), 1894-1952 (Box 67)
    - P, Miscellaneous: Pl (2616-2617), 1895-1954 (Box 67)
    - P, Miscellaneous: Poc-Pop (2616-2617), 1878-1949 (Box 68)
    - P, Miscellaneous: Por-Pos (2616-2617), 1893-1950 (Box 68)
    - P, Miscellaneous: Pot-Pow (2616-2617), 1896-1952 (Box 68)
    - P, Miscellaneous: Pra-Pres (2616-2617), 1892-1951 (Box 68)
    - P, Miscellaneous: Prev-Pri (2616-2617), 1878-1955 (Box 68)
    - P, Miscellaneous: Pro-Pru (2616-2617), 1898-1953 (Box 68)
    - P, Miscellaneous: Pu-Py (2616-2617), 1893-1952 (Box 68)
    - Quill Book Shop (2623), 1922-1929 (Box 68)
    - Quimby, Ralph A. (2623), 1927 (Box 68)
    - Quincy, Edmund (2623), 1929, 1944 (Box 68)
    - Quinlan, James and Mrs. Quinlan (see also Macbeth, William; NMc19/2623), 1895-1924 (Box 68)
    - Quinlan, Walter B. (2623), 1912-1915 (Box 68)
    - Quinlan, Will J. (NMc10/2623), 1908-1924 (Box 68)
    - Quinn, John (2623), 1911-1919 (Box 68)
    - Q, Miscellaneous, 1895-1951 (Box 68)
    - R. G. Dun & Co., 1919-1929 (Box 68)
    - R. H. Macy & Co. (2609), 1914-1927, n.d. (Box 68)
    - R. L. Polk & Co. (2620), 1914-1923 (Box 68)
    - R. W. Pressprich & Co., 1932-1955 (Box 68)
    - Radeke, Eliza G., 1912-1929, n.d. (Box 68)
    - Radyclyffe, Amy (2624), 1926 (Box 68)
    - Railway Express Agency (2624), 1937-1953 (Box 68)
    - Rainsford, W. S. (2624), 1919-1930 (Box 68)
    - Ramsey, Charles F. (NMc10), 1907-1912 (Box 68)
    - Rand, Alice (2624), 1932, 1941, n.d. (Box 68)
    - Rand, Ellen Emmet (NMc10/NMc44/2624), 1912-1915, 1929 (Box 68)
    - Rand Galleries (2624), 1937 (Box 68)
    - Rand McNally & Company, 1927 (Box 68)
    - Rand, Nettie (Mrs. Jacob; 2624), 1946-1956, n.d. (Box 68)
    - Randall, Alex B. (2624), 1921-1922 (Box 68)
    - Randolph, Gertrude W. F. and Grace Fitz Randolph (2624), 1912-1917 (Box 68)
    - Randolph-Macon Woman's College (2624), 1926, 1932, 1942-1959, (4 folders) (Box 68)
    - Ranger, Henry Ward and Estate (NMc10/2624), 1892-1921, n.d., (2 folders; includes illustrated letters 5/21/93, 6/12/93, 5/18/94, 7/23/95) (Box 68)
    - Raoul-Duval, Fannie (Mme. Maurice; 2625), 1913-1916 (Box 68)
    - Raquel-Hirst, Claude, 1893 (Box 68)
    - Rathbone, Georgie W. (Mrs. J. C.; 2625), 1948-1950 (Box 68)
    - Ravenel, Beatrice and Francis G. (2625), 1917-1922 (Box 68)
    - Raught, John Willard (NMc10), 1893-1912 (Box 68)
    - Ravlin, Grace (2625), 1923-1925, n.d. (Box 68)
    - Raymond, Abby M. (2625), 1919-1920 (Box 68)
    - Read, William A. (2625), 1916 (Box 68)
    - Reaser, Willbur Aaron (NMc10/2625), 1897-1942, n.d. (Box 68)
    - Reasoner, David (see also Thayer, Abbot Handerson, Estate; 2625), 1925-1929 (Box 68)
    - Reaugh, Frank (NMc10/2625), 1895-1930 (Box 68)
    - Reckard, Kathryn (NMc10), 1909-1910 (Box 68)
    - Record, Dorothy (2625), 1918-1924 (Box 68)
    - Redd, Fanny F. (2625), 1914, 1922 (Box 68)
    - Redfield, Edward W. (NMc10/2625), 1902-1937, n.d., (3 folders) (Box 68)
    - Redway, Kate V. C. (2625), 1937 (Box 68)
    - Reed, Brooks (Brooks Reed Gallery, Inc.; NMc28), 1915-1918, 1930-1937 (Box 68)
    - Reed, Corinne, 1901-1908 (Box 68)
    - Reed, Josephine B. (Mrs. Victor A.; 2625), 1936-1937 (Box 68)
    - Reed, Lillian R. (2623), 1913 (Box 68)
    - Rees, Soren P. (2625), 1916, 1922 (Box 68)
    - Reese, Albert (2625), 1950-1958 (Box 68)
    - Reichard, G. (NMc19/2625), 1895-1896 (Box 68)
    - Reid, Robert (NMc10), 1914-1930, n.d. (Box 68)
    - Reid, Sarah Bigelow (2625), 1930 (Box 68)
    - Reindel, Edna (2625), 1937-1951 (Box 68)
    - Reindel, William G. (2625), 1932-1937 (Box 68)
    - Reisinger, Hugo and Estate (NMc19/2625), 1910-1915 (Box 68)
    - Reitz, Ralph B. (2625), 1910-1925 (Box 68)
    - Reitz, Walter R. (2625), 1930-1932, 1956 (Box 68)
    - Reitzenstein, E. Lillian (Mrs. H. A.; 2625), 1927 (Box 68)
    - Remington, Frederic (NMc10), 1901, 1906, 1943, n.d. (Box 68)
    - Remsen, Ira (2623), 1926 (Box 68)
    - Reon, Lida A. (NMc10), 1904-1905 (Box 68)
    - Resor, Jane P. (Mrs. Stanley; 2625), 1937-1951 (Box 68)
    - Rettig, Martin (2625), 1923-1929 (Box 68)
    - Reuling, George (NMc19), 1905-1913 (Box 68)
    - Revillon, Joseph W. (2625), 1947-1951 (Box 68)
    - Rexcraft of Washington, 1945 (Box 68)
    - Reynard, Grant (2625-2626), 1930-1958 (Box 68)
    - Rhett, Ruth H. (Mrs. James M.; 2626), 1915-1916, 1930 (Box 68)
    - Rhind, John Massey (NMc10/2626), 1895, 1918-1930 (Box 68)
    - Rhinelander, Frederic W. (2626), 1939 (Box 68)
    - Rhoades, J. Harsen (2626), 1905-1909, 1917-1937 (Box 68)
    - Rhode Island School of Design (NMc19/2626), 1903-1953, n.d., (7 folders) (Box 69)
    - Ricardo, Gracia (2626), 1943-1953 (Box 69)
    - Rice, Sydney (2626), 1929-1930 (Box 69)
    - Rice, William Gorham (2626), 1926-1932 (Box 69)
    - Richard, Jacob (2626), 1921, 1947 (Box 69)
    - Richards, Elias (NMc10/2626), 1915, 1919 (Box 69)
    - Richards, Lucy (NMc10/2626), 1910-1916, n.d. (Box 69)
    - Richards, Theodore William (2626), 1915-1917 (Box 69)
    - Richards, William Trost (NMc10), 1892-1905 (Box 69)
    - Richardson, Mrs. A. M. (2626), 1917 (Box 69)
    - Richardson & Richardson (2623), 1953-1959 (Box 69)
    - Richardson, Constance (Mrs. Edgar P.; 2626), 1946-1953, (3 folders) (Box 69)
    - Richardson, Edgar P. (2626), 1946-1956, 1962 (Box 69)
    - Richardson, Francis Henry (NMc10/2626), 1892-1893, 1913-1914 (Box 69)
    - Richardson, Margaret F. (2626), 1922-1927 (Box 69)
    - Richardson, Mary Curtis (NMc10/2626), 1909-1917 (Box 69)
    - Richmond, Henry Lee and Martha Bullard Richmond (2627), 1926-1930 (Box 69)
    - Ricketson, Oliver G. (2627), 1926 (Box 69)
    - Riddell, Mrs. William J. (2627), 1932 (Box 69)
    - Riddle, C. B. (2627), 1929-1930 (Box 69)
    - Rieber, Winifred (2627), 1910-1916, n.d. (Box 69)
    - Riker, Charles N. (2627), 1930 (Box 69)
    - Riordan, Anna V. (Mrs. Roger; NMc10), 1905 (Box 69)
    - Ripley, A. Lassell (2627), 1926-1948 (Box 69)
    - Risque, Caroline (2627), 1915-1917 (Box 69)
    - Ritman, Louis (2627), 1919-1927 (Box 69)
    - Ritschel, William (2627), 1917-1923, n.d. (Box 69)
    - Rittenberg, Henry R. (NMc10), 1911, 1918 (Box 69)
    - Rivers, Robert Wheaton (2627), 1940 (Box 69)
    - Roanoke College (2627), 1926 (Box 69)
    - Robert Hull Fleming Museum, 1933-1960 (Box 69)
    - Roberts, Elizabeth W. (2627), 1915-1918 (Box 69)
    - Roberts, George (2627), 1925-1929 (Box 69)
    - Roberts, Hugh (2627), 1915-1932 (Box 69)
    - Roberts, Mary Fanton (2623), 1911-1914 (Box 69)
    - Robertson, Chester J. (2627), 1943-1957 (Box 69)
    - Robertson, Francis H. (2627), 1918-1919, 1927-1932 (Box 69)
    - Robertson, Jno. M. (NMc19/2627), 1895-1918 (Box 69)
    - Robineau, Adelaide Alsop and S. Robineau (Robineau Pottery; 2627), 1909-1917 (Box 69)
    - Robinson, Ben Carl (2627), 1914-1915 (Box 69)
    - Robinson, Charles D. (NMc10/2627), 1893, 1899 (Box 69)
    - Robinson, Dent (2627), 1923-1924 (Box 69)
    - Robinson, Edith Dole (2627), 1914-1915 (Box 69)
    - Robinson, Frank T. (NMc20/2627), 1894-1896 (Box 69)
    - Robinson, Mrs. H. E. (2627), 1912-1916 (Box 69)
    - Robinson, Harriett K. (2627), 1940 (Box 69)
    - Robinson, Mrs. Moncure (2627), 1896, 1911-1915 (Box 69)
    - Robinson, Monroe Douglas, 1932 (Box 69)
    - Robinson, Theodore (see also Robinson, Mrs. H. E.; NMc10), 1893-1896, n.d., (includes photograph of Robinson removed to 3.1: Photographs of Artists) (Box 69)
    - Robinson, William M. and Mrs. Robinson (2627), 1930-1937 (Box 69)
    - Robinson, William S. (NMc10/2627), 1890-1895, 1915-1932 (Box 69)
    - Rochester Art Club (A. W. Moore; 2627), 1908-1913 (Box 69)
    - Rochester Exposition (2627), 1913-1916 (Box 69)
    - Rochester, Mary Thomas (2627), 1914-1919 (Box 69)
    - Rockefeller, Mrs. John D., III (2627), 1940-1952 (Box 69)
    - Rockefeller, John D., Jr., and Mrs. Rockefeller (2627), 1932-1947 (Box 69)
    - Rockwell, Elizabeth J. (NMc10), 1893-1896 (Box 69)
    - Rockwell, Kenneth (2627), 1926-1930 (Box 69)
    - Rodgers, Florence M. (2627), 1925-1927 (Box 69)
    - Rodgers, T. B., Jr. (2627), 1929-1932 (Box 69)
    - Rogers, Mrs. Huddleston (2627), 1942-1946 (Box 69)
    - Rogers, William A. (2627), 1908-1925 (Box 69)
    - Roggen, Harry A. (2627), 1925-1926, 1937 (Box 69)
    - Rollin, Horace J. (NMc10), 1904-1905 (Box 69)
    - Rollins, Alice R. (2627), 1930-1932 (Box 69)
    - Rolshoven, Julius (NMc10), 1911-1912, 1919 (Box 69)
    - Roman Bronze Works, Inc. (NMc20/2627-2628), 1908-1929, 1950-1956, (2 folders) (Box 69)
    - Roman, Minna (2628), 1921-1926 (Box 69)
    - Roosevelt, Mrs. Franklin D. (2628), 1930 (Box 69)
    - Root, Edward W. (2628), 1924, 1949-1958 (Box 69)
    - Rorheimer-Brooks Studio (2628), 1912-1913 (Box 69)
    - Rose, Durant and Lillian Tiffany Rose, 1929-1930 (Box 69)
    - Rose, Ethel and Guy Rose (NMc10/2628), 1911-1919, 1937 (Box 69)
    - Rosen, Charles and Mildred Rosen (NMc10/2628), 1908-1916, n.d. (Box 69)
    - Rosenberg, Henry M. (NMc10), 1892-1913, n.d. (Box 69)
    - Rosenberg, J. N. (2628), 1914-1919 (Box 69)
    - Rosenthal, Albert (NMc10/2628), 1906-1937, n.d., (7 folders) (Box 70)
    - Ross, Helen H. and Sanford Ross (NMc47/2628), 1932-1942 (Box 70)
    - Rosseau, Percival (2628), 1929 (Box 70)
    - Rossiter, Mrs. William W. (2628), ca. 1893-1903, 1921 (Box 70)
    - Rost Art Shop (2628), 1944-1952 (Box 70)
    - Roth, Ernest D. (2628), 1926-1927 (Box 70)
    - Roth, Frederick G. R. (NMc10/2628), 1908-1923, n.d. (Box 70)
    - Rothschild, Simon F. (2628), 1913-1914 (Box 70)
    - Roullier, Albert (Albert Roullier Art Galleries; NMc20/2628), 1893-1932, n.d., (2 folders) (Box 70)
    - Round, Mrs. William M. F. (2628), 1907-1913 (Box 70)
    - Rowell, C. B. (Mrs. Frank B.; 2628), 1930-1931 (Box 70)
    - Rowland, T. F. (2628), 1930-1932, n.d. (Box 70)
    - Rowlands, Walter (NMc20/2628), 1905-1920 (Box 70)
    - Royall, Mary and William L. Royall (2628), 1929-1932 (Box 70)
    - Roys, B. L. (NMc10), 1899 (Box 70)
    - Rubens, Gilbert E. (2628), 1932, 1939 (Box 70)
    - Rubins, H. W. (2628), 1914-1915 (Box 70)
    - Ruddock, Austin E. and Claretta Ruddock (2628), 1920-1941, (2 folders) (Box 70)
    - Rudisill, H. T. (2628), 1925-1929 (Box 70)
    - Ruge, Clara (2628), 1903-1925 (Box 70)
    - Rumsey, Charles Cary (2628), 1912-1930 (Box 70)
    - Rungius, Carl (2629), 1921-1929 (Box 70)
    - Runyon, Berenice Agney and Walter Clark Runyon, Sr. (2629), 1918-1927 (Box 70)
    - Rush, Frank P. (2629), 1918-1932, (2 folders) (Box 70)
    - Russel, Mary E. (Mrs. Walter; 2629), 1917-1926 (Box 70)
    - Russell, C. S. and D. R. Russell (see also Russell, Mrs. Charles Marion; NMc10), 1898-1899 (Box 70)
    - Russell, Mrs. Charles Marion (see also Russell, C. S. and D. R. Russell; NMc10), 1902-1911, 1925 (Box 70)
    - Russell, Ernest, 1925-1927 (Box 70)
    - Russell, L. L. (Mrs. Thomas; 2629), 1925 (Box 70)
    - Russell, Sarah H. (Mrs. Lewis; 2629), 1914-1915 (Box 70)
    - Russmann, Felix (2629), 1913-1917 (Box 70)
    - Rutherfurd, R. A. (2629), 1929-1930 (Box 70)
    - Ruthrauff, C. C. (2629), 1898-1912 (Box 70)
    - Rutter, James M. (2629), 1917-1924 (Box 70)
    - Ryan, Clendenin, J., Jr. (2629), 1940-1952 (Box 70)
    - Ryan, Joseph James and Walter B. Ryan, Jr. (2629), 1937-1958, (3 folders) (Box 70)
    - Ryan, Thomas Fortune III (2629), 1951-1952 (Box 70)
    - Ryder, Albert Pinkham (NMc11/2629), 1909-1916 (Box 70)
    - Ryder, Chauncey F. and Mary Ryder (NMc4/NMc11/NMc44/NMc46/NMc48/2629), 1906-1937, n.d., (8 folders; includes illustrated letter 10/17/14 and exhibition catalog 2/27) (Box 70)
    - Ryder, H. R. (NMc11/2629), 1926-1927 (Box 70)
    - Ryerson, Marjorie (2629), 1926-1932 (Box 70)
    - Ryerson, Martin A. (2629), 1912-1927, (2 folders) (Box 70)
    - Ryerson, Mary M. (NMc11), 1909-1910 (Box 70)
    - Ryle, John and Mrs. Ryle (2629), 1937-1941 (Box 70)
    - R, Miscellaneous: Illegible, 1900-1932, n.d. (Box 70)
    - R, Miscellaneous: R-Rap, 1899-1951 (Box 70)
    - R, Miscellaneous: Ras-Ray, 1903-1946 (Box 70)
    - R, Miscellaneous: Rea-Reei, 1899-1955 (Box 70)
    - R, Miscellaneous: Reid-Reic, 1898-1953 (Box 70)
    - R, Miscellaneous: Reid-Rein, 1899-1951 (Box 70)
    - R, Miscellaneous: Reis-Reu, 1895-1943 (Box 71)
    - R, Miscellaneous: Rev-Rho, 1898-1955 (Box 71)
    - R, Miscellaneous: Rice-Richardson, 1904-1955 (Box 71)
    - R, Miscellaneous: Richey-Rig, 1894-1953 (Box 71)
    - R, Miscellaneous: Rik-Rix, 1893-1954 (Box 71)
    - R, Miscellaneous: Roa-Robe, 1895-1957 (Box 71)
    - R, Miscellaneous: Robi-Robs, 1905-1954 (Box 71)
    - R, Miscellaneous: Roc-Rof, 1894-1952 (Box 71)
    - R, Miscellaneous: Rog-Rol, 1902-1950 (Box 71)
    - R, Miscellaneous: Rom-Ror, 1879-1950 (Box 71)
    - R, Miscellaneous: Ros, 1895-1953 (Box 71)
    - R, Miscellaneous: Rot-Roy, 1893-1949 (Box 71)
    - R, Miscellaneous: Rub-Rush, 1897-1951 (Box 71)
    - R, Miscellaneous: Russ-Ry, 1895-1947 (Box 71)
    - S & G. Gump Company (2595), 1905, 1915-1926 (Box 71)
    - Sackett, Clara C. (2630), ca. 1900-1901, n.d. (Box 71)
    - Sackett, John T. (Sackett & Lang; 2632), 1893-1928, (3 folders) (Box 71)
    - Saffarrans, Mrs. A. M. (2632), 1922-1923 (Box 71)
    - Safford, S.E.H. (Mrs. P. H.; 2632), 1930 (Box 71)
    - Sage, Cornelia C. (Mrs. Henry M; NMc50/2632), 1914-1956 (Box 71)
    - Sage, Mrs. Dean and Estate (2632), 1913-1914, n.d. (Box 71)
    - Sage, Harry W. (2632), 1925-1927 (Box 71)
    - Saint Andrew's Church, 1895-1937, (10 folders) (Box 71)
    - Saint Botolph Club (2632), 1911-1918, 1947 (Box 71)
    - Saint Louis Art League (2632), 1909, 1914-1919 (Box 71)
    - Saint Louis Exposition and Music Hall Association (NMc20), 1895-1899 (Box 71)
    - Saint Paul Institute, Science Museum (2632), 1938-1946 (Box 71)
    - Sakai, Barnabas T. (2632), 1898-1899 (Box 71)
    - Salisbury, William (2632), 1926-1937, n.d. (Box 71)
    - Salko, Samuel (2632), 1945-1951 (Box 71)
    - Salmagundi Club (see also box 164; 2632), 1921-1956 (Box 71)
    - Salmon, Walter J. (2632), 1929-1932 (Box 71)
    - Salomons & Stevens (2632), 1893-1895 (Box 71)
    - Saltus, Evelyn and Rollin S. Saltus (2632), 1913-1923 (Box 71)
    - Salvation Army (2632-2633), 1923-1932 (Box 71)
    - Salvatore, Victor D. (NMc11), ca. 1912 (Box 71)
    - Sample, Gladys Humphrey (Mrs. John T.; 2633), 1919-1926 (Box 72)
    - Sample, Paul Starrett (2633), 1930-1932 (Box 72)
    - San Esteban de Canongo, Countess de (2633), 1914 (Box 72)
    - San Francisco Art Association/Museum of Art (J. Nilsen Laurvik; NMc58/2633), 1912-1932, 1950 (Box 72)
    - Sanborn, Charles F. (2633), 1926-1927 (Box 72)
    - Sanden, A. T. (NMc20), 1897, 1903 (Box 72)
    - Sanderson, Clare and Mrs. Lucien Sanderson (2633), ca. 1912-1932 (Box 72)
    - Sandzén, Birger (2633), 1913-1915 (Box 72)
    - Santa Barbara Museum of Art (2633), 1940-1948 (Box 72)
    - Santo, Patsy (2633), 1945-1958 (Box 72)
    - Sargent, E. Adelaide (2633), 1937 (Box 72)
    - Sargent, Helen White (Mrs. H. E.; 2633), ca. 1910-1924 (Box 72)
    - Sarka, Charles N., 1914-1925 (Box 72)
    - Sartain, Emily, Harriet Sartain and Helen Sartain (NMc11/2633), 1907-1913, 1929-1932 (Box 72)
    - Sartain, William (NMc11/2633), 1902-1922, n.d., (6 folders; 11/7 letter includes sketch of map to Sartain's studio in Rome) (Box 72)
    - Sartain, William, Estate (2633), 1925-1929 (Box 72)
    - Satinover Galleries (2633), 1917-1923 (Box 72)
    - Saunders, Kendall (2633), 1914-1918 (Box 72)
    - Saunders, Whitelaw (2633), 1915-1921 (Box 72)
    - Savage, Louise C. (Mrs. Arthur H.; 2633), 1930-1962 (Box 72)
    - Savings Investment & Trust Company (2633), 1916-1920 (Box 72)
    - Sawitsky, William and Mrs. Sawitsky (2633), 1925-1948, n.d., (2 folders) (Box 72)
    - Sawyer, Charles H. and Kitty Sawyer (2633), 1943-1949, 1957 (Box 72)
    - Sawyer, Edith (NMc11), 1897, 1909-1910 (Box 72)
    - Sawyer, Helen (2633), 1932 (Box 72)
    - Sawyer, Philip Ayer (2633), 1932 (Box 72)
    - Sawyer, William H. (2633), 1895-1924 (Box 72)
    - Saxton, Gerard (NMc11), 1908-1909, n.d. (Box 72)
    - Schamberg, Morton L. (NMc11), 1909-1913 (Box 72)
    - Scheffel, Herbert T. (2633), 1946-1947 (Box 72)
    - Schell, Mary E. (2633), 1915-1924 (Box 72)
    - Schenectady Club of College Women (2633), 1923-1927 (Box 72)
    - Schervee Studios, Inc. (2633), 1913-1930 (Box 72)
    - Schieweck, Cecilia (2633), 1917, 1925-1930 (Box 72)
    - Schiff, Jacob H. and Mrs. Schiff (2633), 1900-1932 (Box 72)
    - Schille, Alice (2633), 1925-1926 (Box 72)
    - Schilling, G. A. (2633), 1926-1930 (Box 72)
    - Schleicher, Louise (Mrs. A. G.; 2634), 1944-1946 (Box 72)
    - Schlichting, H. C. (2634), 1929-1930 (Box 72)
    - Schmidt, Karl (NMc11/2634), 1912-1927, (includes Christmas card 12/26) (Box 72)
    - Schmidt, Otto G. (2634), 1926 (Box 72)
    - Schnakenberg, Henry Ernest (2634), 1923-1948, n.d. (Box 72)
    - Schneider, Albert K. (Schneider-Gabriel Galleries, Inc.; 2634) and Estate, 1932-1953 (Box 72)
    - Schofield, W. Elmer (NMc11/2634), 1911-1923 (Box 72)
    - Schramm, Stephen J. (2634), 1932-1937 (Box 72)
    - Schroeder, A. and Mrs. Schroeder (2634), 1919-1921 (Box 72)
    - Schuchardt, William H. (2630), 1926-1930 (Box 72)
    - Schucker, Charles (2634), ca. 1940-1949 (Box 72)
    - Schultheis, Henry (2634), 1912-1937 (Box 72)
    - Schulze, Paul (2634), 1914-1948, n.d., (10 folders) (Box 72)
    - Schuyler, Montgomery (2634), ca. 1908-1915, 1937 (Box 72)
    - Schwartz Galleries (2634), 1920-1932 (Box 72)
    - Schweider, Arthur (2634), 1921-1926 (Box 72)
    - Schweitzer, Gertrude (2634), 1937, n.d. (Box 72)
    - Scott & Fowles (2634), 1930-1952 (Box 72)
    - Scott, Anna Page (2634), 1898-1916 (Box 72)
    - Scott, Lucy P. (2634), 1922-1923 (Box 72)
    - Scoville, Charles Burton (2634), 1914-1915 (Box 72)
    - Scoville, Herbert and Mrs. Scoville (2634), 1911-1913 (Box 72)
    - Scudder, Antoinette (2635), 1925 (Box 72)
    - Scudder, J. A. (NMc11/2635), 1907, 1929, n.d. (Box 73)
    - Scudder, Janet (2635), 1909-1929 (Box 73)
    - Seamans, Clarence W. and Estate (2635), 1896-1920 (Box 73)
    - Searcy, Elisabeth (2635), 1919-1929, 1946-1952 (Box 73)
    - Searle, Helen S. (Mrs. A. L.; 2635), 1916-1919 (Box 73)
    - Sears, Taber (2635), 1924-1932 (Box 73)
    - Seasongood, Murray (2635), 1929-1939 (Box 73)
    - Seattle Art Museum (2635), 1913-1950 (Box 73)
    - Seaverns, Charles F. T. and Mary B. H. Seaverns (2635), 1916-1929 (Box 73)
    - Seay, Pauline B. (Mrs. D. E.; 2630), 1923-1925, 1932 (Box 73)
    - Secor, A. J. and Mrs. Secor (2635), 1920-1922 (Box 73)
    - Security First National Bank of Los Angeles (2635), 1945-1946 (Box 73)
    - Selden, Dixie (NMc11), 1894-1895, 1926 (Box 73)
    - Selden, Henry Bill (NMc11/2635), 1912-1932 (Box 73)
    - Sellers, Horace Wells (2635), 1913-1930 (Box 73)
    - Sells, E. (2635), 1909 (Box 73)
    - Sessler, Charles and J. Leonard Sessler (2635), 1929-1952 (Box 73)
    - Seward, C. A. (2635), 1929-1937 (Box 73)
    - Sewell, Helen (2630), 1930 (Box 73)
    - Sewell, R.V.V. (2635), 1915-1919, n.d. (Box 73)
    - Seydel, L. Victor, 1912-1927, (4 folders) (Box 73)
    - Seyffert, Leopold (2635), 1925-1932, 1949, n.d. (Box 73)
    - Seymour, Frances Lords (Mrs. Origen S.; 2635), 1942-1944 (Box 73)
    - Shackleton, Charles (2635), ca. 1912-1915 (Box 73)
    - Sharman, John and Margaret Sharman (2635), 1915-1929 (Box 73)
    - Sharp, Adelaide (2636), 1921-1930 (Box 73)
    - Sharp, Mrs. W. Z. (2636), 1923-1929 (Box 73)
    - Shaw, Caroline Ryan (2636), 1940, n.d. (Box 73)
    - Shaw, Edwin C. (2636), 1914-1937, (5 folders) (Box 73)
    - Shaw, Samuel T. (2636), 1896, 1913-1924 (Box 73)
    - Shay, Julia (2636), 1924-1925 (Box 73)
    - Sheeler, Charles R., Jr. (NMc11/2636), 1907-1921 (Box 73)
    - Shelton, Ada S. (2636), 1915-1920 (Box 73)
    - Shelton, Harris (2636), 1942 (Box 73)
    - Shelton, William H. (2636), 1922-1923 (Box 73)
    - Shepherd, James G. (2636-2637), 1905-1930, n.d., (10 folders) (Box 73)
    - Sherman, Cathleen (2637), 1945 (Box 73)
    - Sherman, Frederic Fairchild and Julia M. Sherman (2637), 1914-1952, (2 folders) (Box 73)
    - Sherwood, Blythe (2637), 1925 (Box 73)
    - Sherwood, Jean (Mrs. John B.; NMc20), 1900-1910 (Box 74)
    - Shields, E. W. (2637), 1909-1914 (Box 74)
    - Shinn, Everett (NMc11), 1908, 1913, 1937 (Box 74)
    - Shipley, Annie B., 1893-1894 (Box 74)
    - Shipley, Robert M. (2637), 1929-1930 (Box 74)
    - Shipman, Louis Evans (2637), 1924-1925 (Box 74)
    - Shipp, Mary Preston (2637), 1913-1915 (Box 74)
    - Shivler, G. L. (2637), 1911-1914 (Box 74)
    - Shore, Henrietta (2637), 1915, 1929-1930 (Box 74)
    - Shorey, George H. (2637), 1911-1932 (Box 74)
    - Short, Livingston Lyman (2637), 1929-1930 (Box 74)
    - Shufeldt, Frank A., Jr. (see also Walker, A. Stewart and Sybil Walker; 2637), 1920-1926 (Box 74)
    - Shull, Della (2637), 1926, 1930 (Box 74)
    - Shulman, Herman (2637), 1937-1943 (Box 74)
    - Shurtleff, Clara E. (Mrs. Roswell Morse; 2637), 1912-1927, (2 folders) (Box 74)
    - Shurtleff, Roswell Morse (NMc11), 1894-1909 (Box 74)
    - Shuttleworth, Claire (NMc11/2637), 1899-1916 (Box 74)
    - Sibley, Florence (2637), 1923-1924 (Box 74)
    - Sickert, Walter (NMc11), n.d. (Box 74)
    - Siebeneck, Henry K. (2637), 1924-1926 (Box 74)
    - Silva, William P. (NMc11/2637), 1908-1926 (Box 74)
    - Silvermine Tavern & Galleries (2637), 1932 (Box 74)
    - Simmons, Edward (2637), 1921-1927 (Box 74)